Princeton University Library Collection of Ashbel Green Materials, 1744-1958 (bulk 1783-1848): Finding Aid C0257
Manuscripts Division
- Series 4: Miscellaneous, 1789-1858; 2 boxes 27 linear feet
  - Bill of Complaint, circa 1807; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 19)
    Administrator of Elizabeth S. Green, d. 1807 vs. Ebenezer Stockton, Job Stockton and Thomas P. Johnson, executors of Robert Stockton, d. 1805, AMs Ashbel Green
  - Certification: Treasurer of the College of New Jersey, 1818 July 8; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 20)
    Certifying Samuel Bayard, DS by Ashbel Green
  - Genealogical Sketch of the Descendants of Thomas Greene of Malden, Mass, 1858; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 21)
    By Samuel S. Greene. Published by Henry W. Dutton and Son: Boston, 1858. Includes Ashbel Green bookplate, autograph notes, and 2 photographs,.
  - Green Family Tree, undated; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - The Life of Ashbel Green, V.D.M., 1849; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 23)
    Written by Ashbel Green and edited by Joseph H. Jones. Published by R. Carter and brothers: New York, 1849. Includes 1 ADS by Ashbel Green
  - Meeting Minutes: Synod of New York and New Jersey, 1819 October 22; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 1)
    by William A. McDowell to Ashbel Green
  - Meeting Notes, 1789; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 2)
    Committee for the Presbytery of Philadelphia, AMsS
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1828-1896; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 3)
    Advertisements
  - Practical Sermons, Extracted from the Christian Advocate, 1789; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 4)
    By Ashbel Green. Pamphlet printed by John C. Clark of Philadelphia.
  - Resolutions on entering on duty on President of Princeton College, 1812 November 10; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Student Rolls, undated; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 6)
    College of New Jersey student rolls
  - Indenture, 1786 September 22; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 7)
    Immediate Source of Acquisition
    AM 2017-92
    Indenture indicating that William Williams, son of Susanna Williams, was bound to Rev. Ashbel Green for 11 years.